Guide to the Albert F. Murray papers, 1858-1987 MS2003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Television, 1921-1964; MS2003 Series 14; 2 Linear feet
  - Standards: Television Bibliography and RMA Television Standards, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Standards: Television Principles and practice GE Lesson 1-8 Television Reports on FCC Actions, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Torpedo, 1920-1931; MS2003 Series 15; 0.25 Linear feet
  This series relates to Murray's role in the work to develop the under-water radio controlled torpedo by the Hammond Laboratory. The folders date from 1921 through 1928, and include the years Murray worked in the laboratory. The material in the series includes reports with blueprints and photographs, a report dealing with theoretical calculations, the employment agreement between Murray and John Hays Hammond, and a patent application for 1928. One of the more useful folders in this series is the overview covering the years 1920-1924 written by Murray about the project.
  - Correspondence Torpedo Control Equipment Murray worked on radio problems, 1923-1931 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Diagrams of Radio Parts and Newport Harbor, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Employment Agreement between Murray and John Hays Hammond, 1923 July 02 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Hammond Torpedo Experiments [overview and summary], 1920-1924 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Patent Information, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Paper Progress report, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Report blueprints, photographs, and descriptions of the Hammond Radio Torpedo Control apparatus, 1921 April 11 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Report Hammond Radio Controlled Torpedo Report on Investigation of under-water Antennas, 1925 January - March (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Report A Report on the Range Test of the Hammond Radio Controlled Torpedo at the Naval Torpedo Station, 1924 September 18 - December 18 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Report Theoretical Calculations Concerning Radio Control Torpedoes, 1920 November 23 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Report Photographs of Experimental Torpedo Control Receiver, 1921 September 28 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Resume of Progress on Remote control of Naval Torpedoes by Albert F. Murray Research Engineer in charge of control, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Oversize, 1916-1945; MS2003/016; 0.5 Linear feet
  This box contains the same material as in the rest of the collection except that it is oversize and requires specialized storage. The material includes primarily oversize images and posters.
  - Diplomas, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Tintypes of man on unicycle, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Autographed image of Bebe Danials Autographed image of Richard Dix and Albert F. Murray
  - 33rd Anniversary Banquet of the Institute of Radio Engineers Hotel Commodore, 1945 January 25 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "The Tech,", 1916 March 01 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    article
  - M.I.T. Mid-Century Convocation [Pictorial], undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Characteristic of the Earth's Atmosphere [poster], undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - The Electron Tube as an Element Industrial Control [poster], undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - The Resistance Welding with Electronic Control [poster], undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - The Cathode Ray Oscillagraph [poster], undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Radio Frequency Allocation for Western Hemisphere [poster], undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Frequency Spectrum of the Electronic Industries [poster], undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Some Fundamentals of Sound [poster], undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - The Spectrum of FCC Frequency Allocations [poster], 1953 (Box 13, Folder 14)